Donna DiRoma

Darkstar1dd@gmail.com 718-775-2563

Professional Summary

Experienced customer service agent committed to the highest level of service. Excellent work ethic and dedicated to effective use of time management, and "can do" attitude. Ability to work with little or no supervision or as a active member of a team. Adaptable to unexpected changes and duties.

Skills

Customer Relations
Computer Literate
Multi-line Phone System
Insurance Verification

Cash Handling Intake Data Entry Training

Work History

Customer Service Agent 2008-2014

Youngs Medical Equipment Bethlehem PA

Obtain and key enter demographic and insurance data into computer. Verify insurance. Obtain necessary documentation and prescriptions for timely billing to insurance. Obtain prior authorization from insurance. Address questions from customer and obtain co-payment.

Courier, Customer Service Agent 1990-2006

Federal Express Memphis TN

Accept packages over counter. Insure waybill is complete and correct. Work Queues and address issues of bad addresses, lost and damaged packages. Complete cash receipt form. Submit missort report to corporate office. Scan package hold room to insure timely location. Remain up to date on signature release list. Assist couriers as needed.

Admitting Representative 1980-1988

Oregon Health Science University

Interview patient/guarantor and evaluate for charity allowance. Verify third party benefits. Key enter admitting and demographic information to computer. Establish payment arrangement. Explain insurance policy to patient and address any issues or queries. Refer to third party agency when necessary

Waitress/Server 1982 (Second Job-Temporary)

Holly's Restaurant Portland Oregon

Take dinner orders from customers and submit to kitchen. Insure meal is delivered in a timely fashion. Table set up. Attend to diner's needs as necessary.

Dishwasher 1979-1980

Glisan Nursing Home Portland Oregon

Using commercial equipment wash dishes and insure they are clean. Send through again when necessary. Clean surrounding areas in kitchen.

Education

Mt. Vernon High School Mt. Vernon NY Graduated 1970 3.5 gpa Lincoln Technical Institute Medical Assisting Program Deans List for Academic Excellence Graduated 2007

Awards

Employee of the month awarded by Federal Express